This is the DallasCowboys.com
Draft Show,
your war room for insider news and draft
analysis from deep within the confines
of Cowboys headquarters at the Star in
Frisco. Now, your hosts, Vach Lombardi,
Nick Harris, Bobby Belt, Tommy Yarish,
and Kyle Yman's.
Today is Tuesday, April 14th, 2026, and
we are nine days away from the NFL draft
in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Welcome in
to the draft show presented by Miller
Light, the only beer of the Dallas
Cowboys. This segment is brought to you
by your Texas Ford dealers. Ford is the
best in Texas. We've got everybody here
today. Vach Lombardi, Nick Harris, Tommy
Yish, Bobby Belt with Chris Beam in the
back. I'm Kyle Yman's. Gentlemen,
officially into single digits now. Nine
days away. This is coming up quick.
>> I need like six more.
>> You need to just add another day or
another week.
>> Every year I'm like, I need like six
more days. But it's all good. We're
going to be ready to go.
>> You don't need six more days. I do. This
is like behind the scenes. I think it
was week one or it may have been
preseason. We were just like chit
chatting like, "Oh, college football
season's coming up." And Nick is like,
"Yeah, I think I'm already like 150
players from spring study." Like, "What
is wrong with you? What What is wrong
with you?" The thing is like spring
study really means nothing once I get to
like January because like all that stuff
was the year prior. It was more so about
just like
>> but if you had 150 players in August,
>> you're fine 150 players in August
though. I knew 150 that would be in the
draft in August. But yeah, it's Anyway,
>> we all started December 1st. So
>> what I'm trying to do is I'm trying to
watch at least eight games of everybody
in the top 50 and it's just it's taking
me a minute. It is really taking me a
minute. That is the process I'm at right
now.
>> You know what? That what you get. That's
what you get when we in January talking
about top five people. You talking about
well Robert Henry from what's his name?
UTS.
>> Yeah. He could be a guy that you can go
to in the like dog. We talking about top
12 people now. You know what I'm saying?
Now look at you.
>> Nick knows every like multidirectional
religious school wide receiver.
>> What? He went to high school
wide receiver out of
Yeah. It's Northeast Mercy West
Mercyhurst Tech.
>> Yeah. Northeast Pope John II University
or whatever.
>> You know, there's a kid out of Tyler
Junior College. You're an East Texas
guy, so I guess you would know. Anyways,
>> but Votch, did you watch Robert Henry?
Is that why he was fresh on the mind?
>> Hell no. Like Nick just mentioned him.
You know what I'm saying?
>> I ASKED YOU TO WATCH HIM LAST WEEK.
>> WELL, WELL, see Kyle, this I have a a a
strict schedule that I go by. Okay. So,
I'm at 206 players. If I ain't got you,
I ain't got you, bro. You know what I'm
saying? If we get to draft day and at
pick 215 and that person ends up being a
pro bowler, bro, you you deserve it. I
didn't watch a film, dog. My bad. But
for these for the top 206 people I got,
>> hey man, I'm I'mma talk about y'all all
day and hopefully if I ain't got it,
Kyle got it. If Kyle ain't got it, Nick
knows something about you.
>> You got it.
>> Nick Nick know where you went to school
and you played track and all your
records and basketball and all that. We
gonna be fine draft day. But I'm not
going to kill myself trying to get the
301. I'm not Dane. I'm VC.
>> Yeah.
>> You know what I'm saying? See, I got I
got the 200 and now it's all about just
taking notes. That's fine.
>> Like, it's all about the the info from
there. But I need you to get the 207,
please.
>> I want you to watch Robert Henry. I want
you to watch the running back from UTSA.
Just do it for me.
>> You know what? While we doing this show,
while we doing this show, I'm about to
watch Robert Henry.
>> Okay, watch it.
>> Let's run it.
>> A live film breakdown by Vach Lombardi
on Robert Henry.
>> And while y'all breaking down other day
running back and while y'all breaking
down other stuff, I be like, "Damn." You
know what I'm saying? Yeah. And we'll
just Cool. Go ahead, Robert Henry. I got
you.
What are you laughing at back in the
corner over here?
>> I'm I'm enjoying all of this. It's It's
great. It's It's getting close. We We We
just need to go ahead and roll into
draft. Draft needs to get here. There's
way too many scenarios. There's way too
many outcomes that keep rattling through
my brain and there's way too much
calling around and talking to other
people that are not even Dallas related
just trying to figure out like, "Okay,
what's so what's happening here? What
what's going on?" and this just feels
like it could go so many different
directions for Dallas and for really
everybody else.
>> Mhm. So, with that being said, 1 through
11, and this is kind of what's getting
to the important side of things as we
get nine days away from the NFL draft,
is there's a lot of trade up, trade down
scenarios being talked about, but in
order to effectively use your trade
capital and to actually move in a manner
that is beneficial for your franchise
and not going to hurt you in the long
term is you have to know at least to a
certain extent what's going to happen in
front of you based on your
conversations, and this is open to the
to the panel. Based on your
conversations, is it becoming any more
clearer what 1 through 11 is going to
look like in front of Dallas and why
Dallas would need to trade up in order
to avoid a wipeout scenario?
>> I I talked to one person and one person
will be like, "Yeah, I think all three
receivers will go top 11." You know,
there's certainly going to be some
defenders left for you there at 12. And
then I'll talk to another person be
like, "Yeah, it's going to be like all
defense in the top 11." So, no one
knows.
>> No, it's getting worse.
>> It is. when when we said at the top of
the entire draft process and one of the
first shows that we had here is like
this is going to have a ton of parody in
the top 12 that is still remaining the
case. The draft still begins at pick
number two this year. It's is it going
to be Arville Reese? Is it going to be
David Bailey? The Jets going to trade
out of it? You know there it starts at
that point and so from there on I don't
feel like there's any certainties in the
top 12 whereas like in recent years um
you could look at uh you could look at
the top six and pencil it in. So, uh,
you got a nice play over there. Vot.
>> Yeah, man. Watch versus Texas A&M 177
yards. There's this one and he's in his
tall do that against&m and look, he's in
his tall stance. You know what I mean?
So, I'm already sick of running backs in
the tall stance cuz I just assume that
y'all just jocking everybody else. And
boy, that was just this kind of one
play. And look, first of all, uh, Texas,
who this is? Uh,
>> UTSA.
>> Okay, cool. They they they probably
ain't going to be blocking&m all day
like this, but just fantastic. I'm in
the alley right now. Defender come down
and bounce to the outside. Contact
balance. Hey, man. Robin Henry, so far
he's looking nice. We'll go ahead.
>> UTSA put offensive lineman in the NFL.
>> Say that we're talking about here. Don't
put it past him.
>> Well, Albert Regis is a guy that I like.
You know what I'm saying? Tory York and
Tori and York. So, they got some dudes
in the in the front seven now. You know
what I'm saying? But I just happen to
see Albert Regis get washed to the side
there and uh Robin Henry is uh doing
well with his reads and stuff. Go ahead,
Tommy, respond to what Kyle was saying.
>> No, I completely agree with Nick that
this thing starts at pick two because I
think it and by at two, I think they're
e it's either going to be Reese or
Bailey. That's what it seems like to me
that New York's going to do if they
decide to stick and pick. The Cardinals
have so many different ways they can go
too because it can either be
>> all right, we'll just take the
consolation prize of Reer Bailey, which
is not a consolation prize. You're
getting a good football player,
>> or do they want to shore up the
offensive line or they take Maui Noah
three from Miami? I think that would be
a just fine pick. But the interesting
part about this draft is there's so many
players at the nonp premium positions
that are so good that
it do you throw it all out the window or
do we see the NFL stick to what it's
done traditionally to where those
positions of higher value typically in
the draft you just kind of reach on guys
like a Monroe Freeling who we've seen go
to at six a lot in Mox to the Cleveland
Browns or something like that versus
>> hey Caleb DS is has the chance to
revolutionize ize your defense or Sunny
Styles has a chance to man the middle of
your defense for seven, eight, nine, 10
years and just because they're not at
those premium positions that we've seen
in the past like an offensive tackle or
a pass rusher, teams decide to pass on
them. Our friend Vaj says all the time
that teams are not great at drafting.
So, is that is that what this is going
to come down to? It is so hard to get a
clear read on this because I don't know
if NFL teams have a clear read on this.
I think just specifically talking about
Dallas because there's obviously been a
lot of smoke about where they might move
or if they'll stand and pick or
whatever. I think that they're going to
because there's so much uncertainty, I
think they're going to get into the
draft, they're going to look at it and
they're going to watch the way stuff
starts happening. So, like for instance,
if you were to see Sunny Styles, who's
been thought to be highest generally
going five to the Giants, generally
there have been some that have been
high, but if he were to go to the Titans
at four and that all of a sudden starts
shifting a bunch of different stuff
where it's like, all right, well, if
Styles is already going at four and now
who knows what the Giants are doing and
you start seeing stuff like that, that
may cause them to shift and go, "All
right, go out because we're we're going
to start losing people." Or it could be
a case where five the Giants surprise
people and they go, "You know what? Maui
Noah is here and we want to get bigger
in the trenches. Let's go Maui Noah. And
then Cleveland can't move back and then
Cleveland goes you fo and then you start
seeing some stuff happen ahead of you
where you're like we can sit. So I think
Dallas is just going to be like some
other teams going to be watching things
and eyeing it to see how do things fall
ahead of us in the first couple picks
and then we're going to make a decision
to go or not. And I think when you look
at the way the board is stacked in terms
of who's picking where, Dallas to me is
the top candidate, like the earliest
candidate in the draft to want to go up.
>> And so there is a a bit of a benefit of
you might be the highest valued suitor
for one of these teams that's up there.
And if there's not a big buyers market
and there's four teams that want to bail
out, Dallas might be the bell of the
ball essentially for them.
>> And you might get a good deal out of it.
>> Yeah,
>> you might get a good deal out of it. So,
I I think personally for me, um I I know
I've seen some situations where the
Cowboys jump up to three with Arizona or
even four with Tennessee. I for me it
doesn't start until six. I I think with
uh the Cleveland Browns at six, I think
that's your first real opportunity to go
up there and make something happen. Um
you know, and then there's then there's
opportunities at 8, 9, 10, and even 11
if you wanted to just do the one spot
swap with Miami if you feel like they
would take a corner off the board that
you want. So, uh there's a lot of
opportunities. And then if you stick and
pat stick and pick at 12, uh, you better
hope that offensive guys are going in
the top 11. So there's just there's so
much fluidity to this whole ordeal. You
know, people have asked me too, like,
hey, okay, then why not make a trade
now? Why not make a trade now so you
know what it is going into draft day?
It's kind of like Bobby just explained,
you got to see how the board falls. And
it's uh they love wheeling and dealing
on the clock. And so um that's that's
what I would expect. And here in this
draft room or here in this podcast
studio um in uh in nine days we're going
to be taking a look at that camera quite
a bit to see if those phones are ringing
from from the start of pick three pick
four.
>> Let's just like for example
to Nick's point where he says why not
just make the deal now or people ask why
not make just just make the deal now.
Let's say you go were to go up to three
and you were to sacrifice, you know, 12
20 and then 92 and you're going up to
get three and that doesn't even totally
match up on the trade value chart, but
Arizona may be in a place where that's
the best deal they could get. So if you
were to go up to three and sacrifice all
that capital, well then let's say, you
know, Love goes right after that and
then you to Tennessee and then you've
got maybe Lemon, Tate, and Tyson. Maybe
all three of those do go in the top 10.
There's a lot of smoke around Kansas
City and Tyson. There's a lot of smoke
about Lemon Tate to New Orleans and Tate
before that. So, if you start seeing
that, then you're looking at it and
going, "Okay, we just traded away all
this capital because we thought we
wouldn't have anything and now Downs is
sitting there at 12. We could have just
sat there, picked, and then still had 20
and 92."
>> Yeah.
>> And so, I think that that's going to be
there's so much uncertainty about who
may bail out, who's successful in
bailing out,
>> where teams are going to go with certain
things that I think everybody's just
kind of hands off waiting to see where
does this go. Bob, let me ask you
because you love Bailey. Would you
rather have Bailey or And this might be
an easy ass answer, Bailey or downs, do
it at 20, and do it at 92. Because just
looking at my board, Cowboys need
defense and defense is plentiful at 92
and 112. So, so moving up, just me
personally watching watching film on
these, I wouldn't want to move away from
those guys because I think guys in those
ranges can help you a lot.
>> Yeah. If you're guaranteeing me Downs is
there at 12, I'm not moving.
>> Yeah. But if you're telling me downs
would be gone by 10 and Delane will be
gone and you know Styles will be gone
now I'm saying all right what's nine to
go make sure I get downs what's six to
see if I could be in contention for
Styles what's three potentially to see
what's Bailey or Reese whatever the Jets
leave you. So yeah I think that if it's
a guarantee downs is there absolutely
I'm taking downs and then I'm waiting 20
and 92 and I I'm feeling much better
about things. Even if though, and I'm
not the biggest Faulk guy, but I'm just
going to say this for the, you know,
just just to just to say, even if it's
Faulk at 12, I still would take Faulk,
dude at 20, dude at 92, dude at 112,
then shooting the dice on Bailey at
three. And I love Bailey, but I just
think the the Cowboys like they got a
bunch of needs. And I think in that
range,
>> it's a bunch of dudes that can help you.
You can kind of spread it, you know,
spread it out a little bit.
>> I guess the question I guess is that do
you want do you need a couple
contributors? If I told you you could
have two contributors or one game
changer,
>> like I mean it may be a case that the
defense does need two contributors
instead of one game changer. But I think
you are looking at that question if
you're talking about going up to three.
>> And that's that's where I don't think
the conversation should start at three
even though it might. I think it needs
to start at six or nine and then you can
maybe have those conversations cuz then
you have the opportunity to still pick
multiple times. You still get to pick in
the second round or late in the first
round again. So, if you're moving to six
or you're moving to nine, you have the
ability to add a game changer because
you're getting inside the top 10 and
you're going to get one of those big six
names that we've talked about.
>> Or you take a you take that player and
then you turn around, you still get
another contributor in the late first,
early second. If you're going up to
three, you're trading
>> honestly your opportunity to revamp the
defense as a whole to get a
gamechanging.
>> Yeah. So, so the question like for
instance, look at each one of those
spots. Let's say you go to three. Three,
you're probably giving up minimum if you
get a deal even 1220 92
>> or 1220 next year's two.
>> So, yeah, something like that. But let's
just for the sake of say 1220 92 and
then you you keep next year's pick. Um,
if you're going up to three, that's
Bailey or Reese. Right now, people would
trend towards that probably be Reese
because Baileyy's projected to go to.
There's still a lot of Jets people that
are insistent it's going to be Reese,
but let's say it's it's Reese that falls
to you at three. So, do you want Reese
at three or let's say you go up six? You
get six and 39 for 12 and 20. And now
six is I don't know, let's say it's
Downs. Downs at six, 39 is Jake Gold or,
you know, Jake Rodriguez, whatever, one
of those. Um, or you go up to nine, swap
with Kansas City, nine and 29 for 12 and
20, and now it's
>> nine is Delane, 29 is take your pick,
whoever's sitting there at the back end
at linebacker or whatever spot you would
want. Um, or just sit there at 12 and
gamble and then hold on to all your
stuff. Like, I mean, th all those
different scenarios, I think, have
benefits to them depending on how they
fall. It's just a matter of what would
you prefer, what makes the biggest
difference. Yeah,
>> I tell you, no matter what, I'm trying
to draft Robert Henry in the damn six.
>> He's going crazy on the film. I'm gonna
keep watching him. I'm going let y'all
keep talking, but Robert Henry from UTSA
is going crazy. Please, do we have
highlights of Robert Henry? Bam. Do we
have highlights of Robert, please?
>> Well, oh, we don't right now. He said
he'll get to it.
>> Man, we got Robin H. Go ahead. Go ahead.
>> Yeah. I'm telling you, this is why I
wanted you to watch him.
>> I got you.
>> Kyle, can I ask a question?
>> Yes. What's that?
>> Okay. I'm filling in for Vatro now.
filling in for
>> or or just ask for the room in general.
Questions matter.
>> They they've talked like there's been
people suggesting could the Cowboys go
up to three? Mcshay started I think Todd
McShet and then it's it's kind of
chattered some other people more
theoretical than anything.
>> Somebody did it the other day.
>> Let's say they went up to three. Is that
100% Reese or Bailey? Or would it be
three to Styles?
>> Uh it would have to be Reese or Bailey.
>> I would think so. But but if it's Bailey
who's left there, let's say Reese goes
because Reese can play linebacker. It's
Bailey. Bailey is not filling linebacker
for you.
>> We were talking about you need you need
a game changer if you're going up that
high and you're giving up that much
capital. I love Sunny Styles. I don't
know if he's necessarily a I can't say
>> Do you feel like Styles floor right now
is five?
>> Yes.
>> So if that's the case, we're talking
about three six.
>> No, I feel like No, I feel like Styles's
floor is his his ceiling is five. the
ceiling.
>> See, I like I think he could go as early
as Titans
Giants five and then after that there's
a chance he could be somewhere, but I
think it's very narrow.
>> Interesting.
>> I don't think Sunny going to save the
world for you. Like I like him.
>> That's what I mean.
>> And the long term of him is cool, but
giving up that much capital to hope that
Sunny saves the world for you. I
wouldn't assume that Sunny's going to
save the world.
>> You need a 10 sack guy if you're going
up that
>> would Reese play linebacker, you think,
or edge?
>> Edge. Yeah,
>> you would need a guy who to come in and
give you 10 sacks year one. And if he
doesn't, then it's it's not fulfilling
expectations.
>> So the only two guys that can do that
are Ree and Bailey.
>> Well, if it's year one, the only guy who
can do that, I think, is Bailey.
>> It probably is.
>> I don't think Reese 10 sacks is rookie.
>> That's fair.
>> Yeah, I could see that.
>> Lots of
>> I don't think Bailey is neither.
>> Do you feel the same way though?
>> You're a hater.
>> Nah, it's just, you know, pass rushes
year one just get a little weird. But
please, please tell me quick. I I think
Bailey, it would be it may not be easy,
but I think Bailey could get you 10
sacks in year one.
>> Baileyy's pro ready to me. Like that's
ready to go.
>> He's he's only gotten better every year
that he's played in college. And I was
looking at a stat yesterday and then uh
stat nerd Nick Harris countered me on,
but we're going to ignore that. In the
two years that David Bailey played at
the last two years David Bailey played
at Stanford, he started seven of their
22 games,
>> but he led the team in sacks and tackles
for loss and he just continues to get
better and better each year and then he
doubles the sack total going into the
last year of college. Sure, college NFL
is very different, but um I think he's
juiced up. I think he can change games
for you.
>> What was the stat counter,
>> please? The the question I asked back to
him is like, okay, what was the like
sacks per p pass rush snap versus his
year at Texas Tech, which I went back
and looked and the the production that
he did have at Stanford was
significantly higher than if you're
looking at like per on a per snap rate
than it was than it was at Tech. But
that doesn't mean that like his
production was bad. He led the FPS at
sax.
>> Yeah. And to be to be fair at Stanford,
like if you go back and watch the
Stanford tape, he's coming in a lot of
like very obvious pass rush situations.
They're putting him in there like to
like pin his ears back and go.
>> Yeah. And it lead it led me also to the
question of, okay, how many run snaps
was he playing at Stanford? How many run
snaps did he play at Tech last year? And
it made me go back and look at some run
snap stuff. So, I appreciate that,
Tommy. Yeah,
>> you're welcome.
>> Good job, guys.
>> I was just messing with him. But yeah,
no, so I think if you're going up to get
that high, then yeah, it's it's Bailey
or Ree. And I think Bailey fits you
better for what you need now. Uh versus
Reese who can be incredible, but he
doesn't he hasn't had as much time on
task at one certain position. He's been
asked to do so many different things
that you are going to have to be willing
to give him a runway a little bit. I
don't know if this team is in position
to give him that long of a runway. Who
knows how long it'll actually turn out
to be. Yeah. But um if I'm Dallas, I'm
looking at either that six scenario
where you go up to six and you get 39 or
you swap your first with the Chiefs and
hope that they're good with just the
swaps and maybe you throw him like a
fifth or something or sixth.
>> Yeah.
>> And just say hello to your good friends
in the Hunt family.
>> There you go.
>> Tommy, Bobby, do y'all like Bailey more
than um Carter last year? Got drafted by
by the Giants. Do
>> you like him better than Carter?
>> No.
>> Okay.
>> You liked Carter more?
>> Yes. M okay.
>> Carter Carter to me was so much more
ceiling whereas like to me Baileyy's a
little more floor.
>> I thought you were ceiling guy.
>> I like ceiling. I mean it's great. I
love having potential but like Bailey to
me I feel comfortable that Baileyy's
going to be a Pro Bowl player.
>> Okay.
>> We're not fighting. I was just trying to
>> No. Yeah. Yeah. No, I like I I went back
and I was watching Bailey again just
kind of refreshing on him yesterday and
it's just like it underlined everything
that I initially felt about him when I
watched it. He's so I think he's got
such high-end traits to be like a
consistent double digit sack guy. I
think he's got the chance to be a really
really high level run defender. I think
he's he's generally a pretty good run
defender. Um like I know Zack Walchuk
has talked about this like he's a little
more cautious about him against run. I
think Bratis is too. Um, I think
Baileyy's shown to be a really strong
run defender who a lot of his issues I
think are just more about overeagerness
and aggressiveness and, you know,
needing to play a little more
disciplined.
>> If uh Bailey can give you like a James
Pierce type year and look, James Pierce
doing goofy stuff, but like
>> hopefully on the field,
>> just the on the field stuff. If he can
give you a James Pierce type year, then
yeah, I think it's probably worth moving
up.
>> It would be worth I just don't know if
he gonna do that, you know?
>> Yeah. By the way, you mentioned Zack
Wchuk and Brian Bratis. We did get
official word this week that they are
going to be a part of our draft coverage
this year on dallascowboys.com and 1053
through the fan dallascowboys radio
network. So excited to have that.
>> Seven people in nine.
>> We only have five microphones so we'll
have to rotate.
>> Brought us chair in the hallway.
>> Yeah, he'll be hanging out and watching
through the window doing his thing. But
yes, we will get the return of Brian
Bratus and we'll also have uh Zack
Wilchuk on uh draft weekend. So excited
to see those guys back in the building.
All right, when we come back, we've got
some Twitter on the 20. We're answering
your NFL draft questions. When we come
back, nine days away from the NFL draft
right here on the Draft Show.
>> Cowboys fans, when it comes to
navigating the everchanging world of
tax, your business needs a partner it
can trust to tackle even your biggest
tax challenges. Ryan is the largest firm
in the world, dedicated exclusively to
business taxes. Our team of tax
professionals has local expertise in all
areas of tax and can help you uncover
savings opportunities you didn't know
you had. Learn more about how Ryan can
improve your overall corporate tax
performance by visiting ryan.com. Ryan,
the official tax partner of the Dallas
Cowboys.
>> Hey Cowboy fans, Keith Davis here,
former Cowboy Davis into the end zone.
>> You know what separates champions from
the rest? Making the right move at the
right moment. With Blockchain.com,
that's never been easier. The Cowboys
became America's team by striking bold
when it matters most. Now it's your
turn. Invest like your icons with
blockchain.com. Visit
blockchain.com/cowboys
today to get started and learn more.
That's blockchain.com/cowboys.
>> Need a lastminute dish to bring to your
Cowboys watch party?
>> You made it. The game's about to start.
Go for the quality, flavor, and
convenience of a Hillshshire Farm
chapata deli sandwich.
With flavors like italiano, turkey and
bacon, and chicken pesto, these
sandwiches will make any crowd go wild.
found in the freezer aisle.
>> Star Sports Tours is the only official
fan travel partner of the Dallas
Cowboys, offering exclusive game weekend
travel packages with pregame sideline
access and photo ops with current
players, cheerleaders, and Cowboy
legends. You want to stay at a team
hotel, attend the best tailgate party in
Texas, tour the Star, and talk X's and
O's with me, Everson Walls. With Star
Sports Tours, you can visit
cowboystravel.com
to book your travel package today.
>> This is the DallasCowboys.com draft
show.
>> Back here on the draft show this summer,
train where the stars are made. At
Dallas Cowboys youth football and dance
camps, athletes of all skill levels ages
6 to 16 are invited to learn from former
NFL players. and the Dallas Cowboys
cheerleaders step onto the field and
practice like the pros. Register before
May 15th to save $25. Visit
dallascowboys.com/camps
to register. Back here with the draft
show presented by Miller Light, the only
beer of the Dallas Cowboys. Chris Beam,
it is time for some
I heard that in the back. I caught him
off guard.
>> Yo, Kyle, can you
>> Twitter on the 20? Can you imagine some
kid come to the camp and Booker's over
there pushing the hell out of him cuz he
lost a race with him. Can you just
imagine the bad the bad PR we'll get on
there?
>> Oh, it'd be great. I love it.
>> Go sign up. So, uh, Tyler Booker,
>> you you should tell Book that sometime
that he lost. I would love to tell him.
>> Yeah, you should see his reaction.
>> I would love to tell him.
>> We did that last year at training camp.
He didn't respond to it. Well,
>> he'd be all right. Uh,
>> he told he told Sean we can go out here
and race right now if that's the case.
>> No, he would beat me in the race, but
but he pushed the kid over.
>> No, he said my hair went over. He said
that's the rules. And he's like, I
pushed him to like show dominance after
I won. He's like, I'd already won.
>> You got to have maniacs like that. You
know, shouts out to him.
>> The the eye in the sky don't lie. I
don't know if he won or not.
>> Uh, first question is from Maria. She
wants to know how your uh Robert Henry
Jr. film has gone.
>> He's beating the hell out of North Texas
and Kyle don't like it.
>> Yeah, I don't like it.
>> Uh, Robert Henry, I'm I'm seeing some
contact balance, change of direction,
you know what I'm saying? Tall stance.
They they throwing the ball to him. He's
good to go there. Breaking tackles. And
I know that most of his film is like
Temple and you know Tlane and USF or
whatever but just
>> yeah those are some good teams
>> solid teams.
>> Tain was in the college football
playoffs
>> but go watch&m where the the real
football players are and they he's doing
some fantastic things there. So I'm
going to put Robert on my board five or
six or something like that. I like him
there.
>> I had him in the early fifth. So yeah
that's probably where it's at. But I
think he's a steal. He's one of those
guys that could develop. What was that?
>> Don't do that with that little&m where
the real football players are. I've seen
plenty of Jimbo classes bust. So,
>> I'm from Mississippi. I don't have this
Texas beef that y'all be having. You
know what I'm saying? So, I'm not
involved in that. But just
>> also, I hate the group of five slander.
I think the group of five can play some
football.
>> Yeah, whatever.
>> Look at who won the who won the national
championship this year.
>> Indiana, right? Where did most of their
starters come from?
>> James Madison.
So, why didn't James Madison
>> Oklahoma State's going to win the Big 12
this year, so let's just watch that
happen.
>> Conor Wigman and Houston have something
to say about that.
All right.
>> All right. We're moving on.
>> Kevin wants to know. Welcome everybody.
That was terrible. Kevin wants to know,
"Start bench cut for the Dallas
Cowboys." All right.
>> Start bench cut.
>> Kenneth Murray cut.
>> Caleb.
>> Thank you.
>> Caleb DS.
>> I need to bring that bit back.
>> Yeah,
he's going to be back next year. Caleb
DS, Arll Ree, Sunonny Styles. All three
Ohio State guys. Three different
positions.
>> Downs. Reese Styles. Start, bench, cut.
>> If I'm going by my board, then I'm
starting.
>> No, but this is for the Cowboys.
>> I know.
>> Oh,
>> for the Cowboys.
>> Yeah.
>> On their defense.
>> Start. Go ahead.
>> Go ahead.
>> You You got it first.
>> I I would start uh I would start Reese
bench. Um
Downs Cut Styles. If I was going by my
board.
>> Yeah, by the board. Reese down Styles.
>> Ready to play next year. Downs Reese
Styles.
by my board down starts Reese's bench
and Styles is cutting.
>> Interesting.
>> Okay.
>> Oh, we need Yeah, I'm
>> I think I'm with the same three.
>> Uh Michael wants to know who is the best
physical freak to take a fly on on day
three.
>> Oo, physical freak.
>> He said in the seventh, but I'm just
going to say day three because it's hard
to tell.
>> I mean, I can give you a seventh. Um
>> yeah, go for it.
>> Physical freak. I I really like uh we've
talked about Charles Dimmings a lot. Um
I like uh
give me Takario Davis. Um one of those
two palm trees that Washington has on
the outside at corner.
>> I like it.
>> Um 6'4 194. Uh
>> yeah, the physicality certainly shows
up. He's uh Oh yeah, here we go. Here we
go. Look at that palm tree in the red
zone. Getting some red zone work there.
Uh he's the tallest corner in the class.
He's also got the longest wingspan in
the class at 80 feet or excuse me 80
inches and 78
>> 80 and 78 inches. Sorry. Uh it gives him
natural advantages. Uh it makes even the
biggest of missteps and coverage that he
does have. I will say it makes him non
fatal just because of how long his limbs
actually do stretch. I like him more in
his own scheme. Um he doesn't
necessarily have to cover step for step,
but he can use his instincts to
anticipate and then length to attack the
ball. Uh and you see that physicality
really show up at the catch point. But
um sometimes that size and physicality
can lead to p penalties. Uh but overall
I I like Takario Davis. I think if you
get a healthy year under Takario Davis,
he's going to be legit. He only played
seven games last year. Um but before
that, I mean, he was getting first round
box going into the season last year
coming in from Arizona, but um yeah,
he's he's legit. I'm a I'm a Takario
Davis fan.
>> He had kind of like a he had like a
lingering hamstring, right, that kind of
kept him in and out of games.
>> Yeah, it was a um uh Oh my gosh, I just
lost it. There's a rib and a hamstring.
>> Rib and hamstring in 25. Yep.
>> And the uh I thought one interesting
note on him was that he's got a nickname
Bobo.
>> And the reason why he's got that
nickname was as a kid his brothers would
call him that because of his bowl cut.
>> Like a haircut.
>> Okay.
>> They call him Bobo.
>> Might have to slip him to the fifth.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Any other guys? Day three.
>> I've got two for you. Um, one guy we've
tal we've talked about a lot, Kieran
Crawford, the edge from Auburn, 6'4,
253, 32 inch arms. I I think you just
turn on his tape and you see a guy who
who pops off the line of scrimmage. He's
powerful. There we go. Thank you, Chris
Bean. Uh, just can run through
everybody. Good contact balance like you
saw there to be able to get through
blocks and slip through. I think he's
still got some room to grow and you're
going to have to give him a runway, but
I mean, he just pushed that big fella
back with one arm. I know that's like
Ball State or Arkansas State or
something, but nonetheless, I think you
you've got a good player there. And then
uh the other one who is just really
unique athletic profile, but it's
interesting to see if a team can make it
work. Eric Gentry, the linebacker from
USC, 6'7, 221 lbs, 35 in arms.
>> It's going to be an interesting way to
see how he fits in. Is it maybe more of
like a special teams role? But there you
see you see long arms. He's not the
biggest guy in the world. He's going to
maybe struggle to tackle some of the
bigger guys and get off blocks, but if
you put him near receivers, he's going
to be able to stretch those big arms out
and knock down passes if he's near the
line of scrimmage. We saw him do it a
little bit at the Shrine Bowl, and he
did some reps like that on tape uh in
game settings this year as well. So, an
interesting seed way way to see if that
works out there, but there's a couple of
guys just athletically that make uh
catch your eye a little bit.
>> You said the not the biggest guy in the
world. Well, I've got one of the biggest
guys in the draft. How about Markeel
Bell, offensive tackle out of Miami?
>> Too big.
>> I don't think so.
>> It's humongous, man.
>> I really don't. I think he's raw. Like,
in terms of his his talent level.
>> He's got a unique size profile. He's
6'9, 346 pounds, which is just insane to
say the least. Zero star recruit out of
Mississippi. Small school in
Mississippi. Why was he not recruited?
Because of his size. He goes to a
community college. uh went the Jo route,
went to Holmes Community College,
>> and then Mario Crystal Ball, picked him
up, named him the human skyscraper, and
he's I mean, he has the one starting
experience, one year of starting
experience at the division one level.
His height works against him because
he's got the high pad level, loses a ton
of leverage, his feet drag behind a bit
because of uh the the movement and how
long he is, too. bigger body, harder to
move laterally, but I think he pairs
some of that size well with the power
and the hand placement and his technique
isn't perfect, but it's refined enough
to where I think he can continue to
learn and he can continue to add to it.
Do you see something different on your
end?
>> Uh, no, not necessarily. I think he does
carry that size. Well, it just kind of
reminds me of the Cameron Williams
situation from last year. Cameron
Williams wasn't as tall, granted, but I
just felt like there was some bad weight
there. Kind of feel the same about
Markeel Bell. And I don't know how you
necessarily shed bad weight from a 69
frame and still retain an ability to be
uh powerful on the edge, but um it he I
I would like to see you said he's 346. I
would like to see it at like 326. And I
know you're asking him to be lean in
that scenario, but
>> 20 lbs drop for a 6'9 offensive tackle.
>> 6'9 and it's tough. It's it's that's
that's where it gets tough for
>> He moves well though. Like he really he
moves laterally. Okay. straight line
speed. He moves for 6'9.
>> Miami's offensive line coach, Alex
Mirbal, one of the best, if not my
favorite in college football. So, I I
will trust the development with Alex
Mirball over anything. Um, that's uh I I
have a third round grade on Markel Bell,
but overall um there was there would be
some things that I think he would need
to clean up before being ready to start.
I would say
>> you have them higher than I do. I have
them in the fourth. I was thinking day
three.
>> We're just we're talking physical freak
flyers basically.
>> Yeah. Yeah. On day three,
>> Lorenzo Styles.
>> Oh, yeah. That's a good one.
>> Like it's there's enough evidence that
says that that family produces football
players and uh a ridiculous athlete with
next to no instincts it feels like when
you watch him play football. But um a
guy who's also converted from receiver
in recent years. And so um I mean that'd
be a total project and probably somebody
who goes close to seventh round I would
guess. But uh Lorenzo Styles is one that
if you just want to go on traits, it's a
good one. Are you playing him at safety
or are you moving him around a little
bit?
>> Uh, I think that like there's a an
inclination from some teams I think that
want to play him at corner.
>> Yeah, I think I would probably try him
at corner.
>> His is measurables match up for corner.
>> Yeah, I I would want to try it there and
see what happens.
>> It's a lot easier freelance in certain
looks as a corner than it is as a
safety.
>> Agree. Yeah.
>> You got anybody watch?
>> I was going to say Marquel Bale, but um
you know you could just take any 6 foot
seven plus tackle. So like Isaiah World
guys like um D pounds or like Crown Over
or whatever like all those guys are like
taller and if you like fix knee Ben and
like footwork and stuff like that th
those guys could turn into decent
tackles for you. Um I just have a hard
time with the taller guys you know
because I just value knee bend so much
and with with them being so tall they
have to be super extra good at knee
bend. So they work on those things
they'll be fine.
>> I like Demetrius Crownover tackle from
Texas A&M. He's a converted tight end.
He
>> over media.
>> Uh there you go. He uh he entered the uh
he entered college station as a tight
end transition to tackle. I I want to
see him use his size a little bit more
though.
>> Yeah, for sure.
>> Be a lot more physical, but I I don't
feel like he uses it to his full
advantage just yet.
>> Lane wants to know, let's say if the
draft gods smile on you, you get Sunny
Styles and Caleb DS both available at
12,
>> which just Yeah, that's a big smile from
the draft gods.
>> Are you thinking about moving back at
least one spot? No man. or just taking
one of your top two guys.
>> I'm just I'm just taking downs. I'm
thanking the draft guys. I'm not going
to get greeted with the draft guys. I'm
taking downs and I'm getting and and
look, I I I know you need linebacker. I
understand that there's a pressing need
for linebacker, but I just got down so
much higher on my board. I just think
downs is probably going to help you a
lot more day one than Sunnywood. Robin
Henry still going crazy Colorado State
right now. So, I'm just going to go
downs there and just let
>> the next team get lucky. like the Ravens
or something get um Sunny.
>> Uh yeah, I mean go down if you can go
down one. I mean there's no harm in that
if you if you've got to if you've just
got like coin flip. I I don't even I
mean they did that with Micah and Rashan
Slater years ago where they were like
okay we know one of them will be there.
We'll let somebody decide for us. Both
of them were there.
>> Yeah.
>> But um yeah, for me I would take downs.
I think they would take styles.
>> So you would clearly take downs?
>> Yes. What I'm saying is is if you trade
back and they take downs now you like
>> you may like Sunny, but I love downs. I
like I like Sunny. So
>> I love both.
>> So Nick loves both. So just me.
>> So just me in particular, I don't want
somebody to make the decision for me.
I'm taking the safety that I think can
change everything with this DC that does
calculus and it all depends on what he
would do. I'm just going to take downs.
I I do think Sunonny Styles is pretty
close to like when you study some of the
stuff that Christian Parker's talked
about and you see the trees that he's
come from.
>> I think Styles checks a lot of boxes for
what they would look for a linebacker.
>> Yeah, that's a good point.
>> I think DS would check a lot of the same
boxes for what he likes in a nickel or a
safety.
>> Talk to him, Tommy. Look at him when you
say talk to him.
>> I'm just saying look me in the eye. I'm
not fighting with you. I'm just saying I
think DS does a lot of the same things
can fit.
>> Do you disagree that they would take
Styles over down?
Uh,
>> I think they would. I think if both of
them are there, I think they take
styles.
>> Yeah, I agree.
>> Right. So,
>> is that just because of bodies?
>> You've added Jaylen Thompson, you've
added PJ Lock, you've added those guys
at safety. You haven't done anything at
linebacker.
>> Yeah. I mean, if you don't if you if you
don't have Caleb DS, you're starting
Jaylen Thompson and Malik Hooker. If you
don't have Sunny Styles currently,
you're starting De Marvin Overon and
Justin Baron or Shemar James. Yeah,
>> I think Baron might actually fit more
some of what they typically have looked
for in that scheme than Shamar James
does.
>> That's a fair point.
>> Kind of along similar but a little bit
different lines. Eric wants to know
>> who is the best fit among potential
later round safeties for Dallas and what
they've been looking for. Uh he he
listed these guys. Ramsay out of USC,
Wheatley out of Penn State, Clark Smith.
Who else could possibly be there as a
fit for Dallas? Let's kind of hone in on
this. 92 112 that range.
>> Yeah, Traden Stukes out of Arizona. Did
you mention him as one of those guys? I
I think he's the most versatile DB in
this class. He can play anything. I I
think you throw him at nickel, safety,
free, strong, outside corner. He can
play literally anything in the secondary
in my
>> A lot of teams have him as a corner.
>> Yeah, I have him as a safety personally.
Um I I feel like I I want to maximize
his range and so that's that's where I
would place him at the next level, but
um he's he's shown all of it and uh that
that would be a guy for me if you're
looking in that 92 102 range. I also
have Jaylen Kilgore as a safety. I know
he played more corner at South Carolina.
Um but I I feel the exact same way about
I I feel like if you maximize his range,
he'd be he'd be better fit in that that
type of range. Mhm.
>> I think you throw Wheatley from Penn
State in there, uh, would be great with
that at 92.
>> You think he even falls to 92, though?
>> I doubt it.
>> I have a second.
>> He might go I don't know if he'll go
like I don't know if he'll go in the
second, but if he's in the 80s, 70s to
80s range, I wouldn't be shocked at all.
>> Okay.
>> Um, another guy that you may hope falls
there is Hulsey from LSU. I I don't know
if he does.
>> Um,
>> I would do triple back flips.
>> Yeah, I I'm like Kilgore from South
Carolina as a safety, too. Bud Clark
from TCU I think would fit. There's so
many of these like third to fourth round
gradedish safeties that would be
fantastic. Is that how you're stacking
your board? Is it Wheatley, Huly,
Clark? No, it's uh it's Huly, Wheatley,
Kilgore, Clark,
>> Stokes, Ramsay. I think I might have to
go back and rewatch Stuks though.
>> I like Stuks a lot as well. How would
you stack your board V? So I'm going up
to the second round. So I got Theamman
and right after Theamman and Wheelley's
there for me. I got Wheelie.
>> You got him in the second two.
>> Yes. I got him higher than Magneil
Warren. I just value range in that way
and and as a rangy dude, Wheelley's like
up there for me. Then in the third
round, I got uh Clark from uh TCU,
Hollyy. Then I got Kyle Lewis. Some
people may have Kyle Lewis as a
linebacker. I think he's a
>> lot I think majority teams have Lewis at
linebacker.
>> Okay, cool. Just on my board. I got him
here. And um Kante Scott Kant Scott from
Miami. That's the That's the end of my
third round. you have as a safety.
>> Can I say Scott? Yes, sir. Okay.
>> You're talking day three.
>> Yeah.
>> Bishop Fitzgerald.
>> He's a great player.
>> Fitzgerald like I mean I think by the
way there's enough about him that I
think makes sense for like on the
coverage aspect of what they're looking
for that
>> I think some of the the run instincts
that at times can seem a little
deficient. Like he'll tackle well, but I
mean just in terms of the read and react
stuff in the run game that is a little
deficient. I think that it's stuff that
they could work on and and feel good
about. And so I think he's a if you're
talking about mid round day three
sometime, that's a name.
>> You think he's pretty close or maybe
even better than Ramsay?
>> Yes.
>> Fitzgerald.
>> Yeah,
>> I'm with you.
>> Good stuff. All right, that does it for
us here on Twitter on the 20. When we
come back here on the draft show, want
to talk a little bit about trade
fallouts. What would it look like at 92
if Dallas has to trade up and go get
somebody? So, what are you okay picking
at 92 if you only maybe have one swing
at it in the first round as opposed to
two first round picks? More to come on
the draft show right after this.
>> Star Sports Tours is the only official
fan travel partner of the Dallas
Cowboys, offering exclusive game weekend
travel packages with pregame sideline
access and photo ops with current
players, cheerleaders, and Cowboy
legends. Want to stay at a team hotel?
Attend the best tailgate party in Texas?
Tour the Star and talk X's and O's with
me, Everson Walls. With Star Sports
Tours, you can visit cowboystravel.com
to book your travel package today. Hey
Cowboy fans, Keith Davis here, former
Cowboy KEITH DAVIS INTO THE END ZONE.
>> You know what separates champions from
the rest? Making the right move at the
right moment. With blockchain.com,
that's never been easier. The Cowboys
became America's team by striking bold
when it mattered most. Now it's your
turn. Invest like your icons with
blockchain.com. Visit
blockchain.com/cowboys
today to get started and learn more.
That's blockchain.com/cowboys.
Need a lastminute dish to bring to your
Cowboys watch party?
>> You made it. The game's about to start.
Go for the quality, flavor, and
convenience of a Hillshshire Farm
chapata deli sandwich.
With flavors like italiano, turkey and
bacon, and chicken pesto, these
sandwiches will make any crowd go wild.
Found in the freezer aisle,
>> Cowboys fans, when it comes to
navigating the everanging world of tax,
your business needs a partner it can
trust to tackle even your biggest tax
challenges. Ryan is the largest firm in
the world dedicated exclusively to
business taxes. Our team of tax
professionals has local expertise in all
areas of tax and can help you uncover
savings opportunities you didn't know
you had. Learn more about how Ryan can
improve your overall corporate tax
performance by visiting ryan.com. Ryan,
the official tax partner of the Dallas
Cowboys.
>> This is the DallasCowboys.com draft
show.
Back here on the draft show, it's time
for the legendary Dallas Cowboys draft
party presented by Miller Light. Join us
Thursday, April 23rd at 6 PM inside Ford
Center at the Star in Fris. Watch first
round picks live on the field. Meet
players, see the Dallas Cowboys
cheerleaders perform, enjoy music,
drinks, and a whole lot more. Admission
is free. Visit dallascowboys.com/draft.
Hope to see you out there. And then
bring your headphones, listen to the
draft coverage as we roll along on the
Dallas Cowboys radio network. It will be
all five of us, FC Lombardi, Nick
Harris, Tommy Yarish, Bobby Belt, Chris
Beam in the back. I'm Kyleman's. We'll
also add Brian Bratis and Zack Walchuk
for that weekend. Cannot wait until next
Thursday. It's going to be a legendary
time. Lots to kind of sift through even
between now and then as
>> we might, I've heard we might get a
Bobby Belt appearance on day three this
year for the first time in three years.
Well, I was here. I just No, it was
three years ago. Yeah. Yeah, that's a
call back. I always have to throw that
dig in there.
>> Yep.
>> Until you come in.
>> Robinson from Texas just went
>> Oh, good stuff. Somebody earlier said
that uh when you were talking about
Robert Henry,
>> they used the word that Brian used last
year. I'm I'm not going to use it. You
know, you remember they they used that
word. He had that type of stance.
>> Who said that?
>> Yeah. I was like, "That's a great call
back."
>> Robert Henry does sound like a division
three Virginia college, though.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it does. Like George Mason.
>> Yeah.
>> Robert Henry. I think there's a Patrick
Henry out there.
>> There's a Robert Morris.
>> Yeah. See?
>> Yep.
>> Just combining the two. That's all.
>> Uh, all right. Trade fallout. Let's say
Dallas does trade up. Let's say they
they do package 12 and 20. and they go
get themselves a dude on inside the top
10, not counting what they would get in
return in the second round, right? Where
do you feel comfortable using your third
and fourth round picks 92 and 112 to try
and maneuver what you're unable to get
because you traded up and don't pick
twice in the first round?
>> What did you pick?
>> That's my question, too. Gotcha.
>> Let's Let's run a scenario for each one
of them, then. Let's run a scenario.
Let's say the most likely for me is
let's say Styles at six,
>> right? So you take a linebacker.
>> Where do you feel comfortable picking at
92?
>> If they took Sunny Styles at six, I want
to go pass rusher at 92. I'm going Max
Llewellyn edge from Iowa. I like him a
bunch. Uh he's a he's a he's a ready
made pass rusher now. Counters and all
that kind of stuff. Not the best run
game dude, but you can teach him how to
do run game stuff. He can play four eye
as well. They also do that with him. And
um hey, he's just uh he's just a just a
bad boy. And you want one for 112 as
well?
>> Uh you can if you have it,
>> man. 112 real fast, man. Shoot. I'll
take Genesis Smith from Arizona. No, we
just took we took a linebacker.
>> You just took a linebacker.
>> Jesus Smith, free safety from Arizona.
>> Okay. So, that's how you address your
your three biggest needs.
>> Range as hell, get picks, um follows
routes well, takes away crossers. Uh he
don't want he don't want to tackle
nobody, but he got size to work on that.
So, those are my guys. I think I think
you could get lucky with Romelo Height
at 92.
>> That was the name I was thinking.
>> And then at 112 at 112, man, sign me up
for some Jaden Kennedy. Uh the nickel
out of Oregon. I am such I tweeted out
last night. I can't get enough of Jaden
Kennedy. Uh I this this guy's legit. Um
and so I would take uh Jaden Kennedy at
112 in that scenario.
>> Okay.
>> But some other corners if you're looking
there, let's say Kennedy, someone else
or another team likes him as much as I
do. Chandler Rivers I think could be
there. The nickel out of Duke. Mhm.
>> Um Dalon Everett I think need a nickel
out of Georgia. So I I think that's a
sweet spot if you do want to go find
your nickel corner.
>> I would also probably lean pass rush at
92. I'm good with height Texas Tech. I'd
be okay with Derek Moore Michigan. Um
maybe Jan Baram Michigan too. I know
this team loves their Michigan players
and the fan base certainly loves them
too. Um, and then yeah, if you can get a
corner or one of those safeties at 112,
Chandler Rivers, I I like Rivers more
than I like Kennedy. I just think
Kennedy's a little too small. Um,
>> he's bigger than Rivers.
>> Yeah,
>> I don't know if he's more filled out. I
don't know if he's more filled out than
Rivers, though.
>> That's what I meant to clarify.
>> Okay.
>> Um, and I think Rivers is just a real
deal thumper. Um,
safetywise in that range, there's a
couple guys you could convince me on.
Um, if Clark is there, if it's Gerald or
Ramsey from USC,
I think you go pass rush first and then
look somewhere in the secondary, whether
it be corn or nickel, if you add one of
those safeties that can do a little bit
of everything.
>> Would you consider a guy like Will Lee
at 112?
>> Yes, if he's there.
>> I watched more of Will Lee literally
yesterday. It's funny you bring this up.
He gives up so many big plays. He does.
>> Oh my gosh. Like that Notre Dame game, I
that was the first time watching it for
me uh since the game happened and I
remember Notre Dame having big plays and
I was like, "Oh, that was who was giving
them up." He gave up like something like
170 yards in one-on-one coverage in that
game. The big plays are tough. He's
physical off the line, don't get me
wrong. He's physical off the line. I
feel like his footwork is solid. I feel
like he does uh match uh routes pretty
well, but the top end speed just really
lacks. And he can get beat over the top.
Even with double moves, he can get beat
over the top, too. Um I I that one would
be a bit of a reach at 112. Um I I
formerly really liked Willie. I had a
third round grade before I watched that
game specifically, and that game really
scared me. And then I started looking
back at some of the other big plays he'd
given up over the year, and it was a
consistent trend of teams just being
like, "Hey, we're going to beat him over
the top." And they did.
>> He struggles out of that like that fade
route, just having to turn and run. But
there were also times where he it looked
like he just lacked focus late in games.
Yeah. Like he was just out of a game and
fatigued. That's that's where I had a
problem. And that Notre Dame game was
the one I was referencing specifically.
I wrote it down right here. Said
fatigued, lacks focus when things got
into late game scenarios and that's
where he gave up multiple big plays late
in that game.
>> I did say he could do really well in a
system with a really good pass rush in
front of him, but and like the ball's
coming out quick, but overall I just
don't see him as a long-term starter.
He's he's a flyer you take in the fifth
if he's somehow there in the sixth and
he'll give you special teams value
absolutely day one. Um but nah I don't I
don't know if you're if you're looking
at 112 I just think there's going to be
other options that are better for you.
Julian Neil out of Arkansas. Devin Moore
out of Florida.
>> Ephesians Price out of Washington. We've
talked about him quite a bit. Another
one of those palm trees at Washington.
Um but
>> uh how do you all feel about Gabakis if
he's there at 92? I am just such a huge
fan of Gabby. I can't get enough of him
at Drusher out of Illinois. Um,
powerful, sets the edge in the run game
really well. He's got some pass rush
upside and he's started to prove it late
in his uh uh final year at Illinois. Um,
I'm a huge fan of Gabe Yakis.
>> I have him early fourth. So, that would
that would feel good at 112.
>> Botch mocked him in the first round when
we were doing the group mock. He uh he
assigned him to somebody.
>> That was one of his crazy picks.
>> Yeah. Well, well, cuz teams suck at
drafting generally. So, yes.
>> I don't think that's a suck at drafting
pick
>> in the first round. In the first
>> I really don't. I really don't. I I I
have a second on him.
>> I think there's a little half of Yakab.
>> That is that is the most common feedback
I've heard from people around the league
is Yak is second.
>> Yeah.
>> Really? I love Yak.
>> So So the media may not be as high on
him as some teams are.
>> Yeah. No, like I think that and that's
that's
>> So that's what it that's that's nothing
>> you're higher than we are.
>> That that's our boy Gabe. That's nothing
Dallas related at all. That just a
couple people I've talked to outside of
here about Yakis, they've said second
universally.
>> He's got a good motor. He doesn't really
quit. Got a got the size advantage. He
looks the part. Got a lot of things
going in his direction. Do you have him
or Malachi Lawrence hire at UCF?
>> Uh I have Lawrence.
>> I got Lawrence hired.
>> Yeah, I do too. Uh Zion Young, Missouri.
>> Lower.
>> I got him right up under Young.
>> Uh I'm just throwing names that are
around him.
>> I did ask one of those people that I
talked about Yakis. They said that Yakis
was higher than Lawrence.
>> Uh Max Llewellyn lower.
>> Okay.
>> I got Llewellyn higher than Yakas. Yeah.
>> Mason Rig. He's further down.
>> Lower.
>> Yeah. Kron Crawford. Reagan nice. Lower
>> or Mason Thomas. Lower. Like I Gabe
Yakis here.
>> I probably end up with Crawford under
Yakis.
>> Lower.
>> I got height. I got See, I think I think
I think too many people low on height
though. I think I think Melo is nice and
and and I, you know, I ain't fuss or
nothing like that, but I just need to
understand people's logic with the he's
older so I'm going to draft him later. I
don't understand the logic. Maybe I'm
just an idiot, but if you could play,
you can play in my mind, right? And
maybe you don't have the the long-term
vision of them, right? Like some of
these guys signed their second contract
when they're 26. So that ain't going to
be the case with Melo for sure, but I
don't think that Melo's film equals a
third round guy. I got a two on him and
I like him a lot. And I think he's right
up there with our Mason Thomas, Cashes
How, and Malachi Lawrence. I I just
Bobby, can you help me out with that?
Like why why is it that the 25 year old
dude falls?
>> Um
>> cuz Messador is also nice, but he falls
cuz he's 25 for whatever reason.
>> Yeah. I mean, I think a lot of times you
got to think about, for instance, there
was a uh a very prominent pass rusher
who uh was talked about as getting dealt
this off seasonason that did not.
>> Um,
>> good job.
>> And that that a lot of the discussion
was the talk of like,
>> you know, very getting getting close to
30s here and and like being able to come
on, it's the one. Uh, so a lot a lot of
talk about like getting close to 30s
here, guys. That that's that's
significant. So you're talking about
when you if you draft somebody in the
first round for instance like Mezador.
>> Yeah.
>> After you've engaged the fifth year
option, he's 30.
>> Like I mean that that's he's in the
rookie deal and you already feel like
all right he's like edge rushers will
slow down into their 30s. But wouldn't
wouldn't the logic be if if he could
really play like if he can really play
I'll take those ridiculous five years
and just be like all right just time to
find a new dude when the deal is up you
know you know in an ideal world you
would like for somebody to play 12 years
for you but like
>> not even 12 years just you generally
think draft somebody thinking second
contract.
>> Sure. But like what if they just
fantastic for five years and the Cowboys
their Cowboys window and I'm saying
window cuz everybody's contract was is
is like three years now. this this team
picked a 25year-old in the top five and
he played 16 years in the NFL Newman. So
I mean they've
>> they've done that before. I don't I
don't necessarily think like there's a
an avenue where Mezador maybe ends up
here and if that's the case then like I
mean they did take a 25-year-old in the
first round. So um it just kind of
depends I think especially in terms of
how teams view it. A lot of teams
probably would have been put off by
Calvin Ridley being almost 24 years old
when he was coming out.
>> Yeah.
>> And so it it I think the position also
matters where you're talking about. You
don't want to generally draft a
25-year-old running back for instance.
>> Yeah. For sure. For sure. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
>> Uh let's let's switch up the scenario
here.
>> You take an edge rusher in the first
round.
>> Okay.
>> And now you got to attack your
linebackers or your safeties corners in
92 and and 112.
>> That's perfect, Kyle. I'm taking Jacob
Rodriguez cuz that's where he belongs in
the third round. People going to hate
it. And uh in the fourth round, man,
I'll take
>> Bishop Fitzgerald or something. You know
what I'm saying? Keep that keep that
safety theme. So, I'm a pass rusher, my
linebacker, and I got a safety there.
>> They're showing uh Jacob Rodriguez film
on the line here.
>> Shouts out to him.
>> Yeah, Nick.
>> Yeah,
>> same kind of names for certain
positions, but
>> if I'm going linebacker, I'm probably
going Josiah Troder or Caleb Elarms or
out of TCU. Josiah Troder out of
Missouri.
Uh, that would probably be a 92 or a
112. I'm just going to do 92 or 112 for
these. And then I I again, I'm going to
hammer this. I still feel like that 9212
range is a sweet spot for nickel. I
really do think you could get a really
solid nickel in that range. Um, it's
about where they drafted Jordan Lewis
back in 2017. It was in the back end of
the third round if I can uh remember.
>> I think he was 92. I think he was pick
92.
>> Uh, pick sele Sorry. Uh,
>> let's go. Let's go. Let's go. See if
your internet's fast today. Hell no.
>> Draft pick selection, not interception.
>> Cheeto was like 54.
>> He was 92. Jordan was 92 overall. So, um
I spot I do feel like and with this
draft specifically, I do feel like
that's a that's a sweet spot that they
could grab him. Um
>> safety if you're looking in that third,
fourth round a few Kilgore. Um yeah, Bud
Clark, Traitton Stokes.
>> Yeah, Bobby, let me ask you something.
What do you think the Cowboys like?
Davidson Ebanosen.
>> Davidson Eiganosen.
>> Thank you.
>> Um I I don't know. I would imagine given
what I know about him and know about the
way that they think, I would imagine
that they are fond of him as a like
potentially late two early day three
guy. But I I don't know specifically
what they would think of him. But I I
think I think that he's checks box. I
got to say if they take an edge rusher
and then they don't have another pick in
the second round, linebackers a big
enough need to me right now that that's
just what I do in the third and the
fourth.
>> Yeah.
>> I just take two and then figure out
which one of them's better.
>> Like he's size, length, can tackle,
cover, nickel, outside. He he he does
all of it. So I'm just curious like why
we haven't been saying his name a little
bit more.
>> Thank you.
>> Probably say early day three
>> for Igbonosen. Man, I got third round.
>> I got a second on him. I'm a huge Ignos.
I texted Tommy and Bobby about Ignosin
yesterday because I was trying to track
down why he's not higher. Um,
>> technical stuff, you know what I'm
saying? Technique stuff, you know, but
you know, but I but he's long and
physical.
>> The flags went down considerably in 25.
Like it looks like that part off the
field stuff.
>> Oh yeah, my bad.
>> Like it was like wait a second.
>> Yeah.
>> NOT A GREAT SIGN THAT WAS HEAVILY.
>> Not a great sign when you have both. Um,
real quick, Troder, Missouri 92, you
think?
>> Yeah,
>> I got a two on.
>> I have a two on him, too, I think. Yeah,
he probably go before that earlier than
that. Um,
>> yeah, I just wanted to clarify. Look at
me.
>> No, no, no. I was saying I have a two on
>> I say this about Davis and Egypos. He
had a sevengame stretch during like the
heart of Big 10 play last year where he
only allowed five receptions for 43
yards. And I went back to specifically
and watched five of those seven and it
wasn't like he wasn't being credited for
things he should have been credited
with. I I love Igmanos. having a CB5.
I'm a I'm a big Ignosin guy.
>> But you did say Big 10. So which Big 10
offenses were those?
>> That's fair.
>> He's playing against Iowa.
>> Oh my gosh.
>> Special teams will score more touchdowns
than they will.
>> All right. Well, that's going to do it
for us here on the Draft Show today. We
will be back on Thursday, 11:00 a.m.
Central time to continue breaking it
down. will be one week out from the NFL
draft for Vach Lombardi, Nick Harris,
Tommy Irish, Bobby Belt, Chris Beam in
the back. I'm Kyleman saying so long
from the Draft Show. We will see you on
Thursday.
>> This has been a production of Dallas
Cowboys.com and the Dallas Cowboys
Football Club.
>> How about this?